Some secrets should stay buried.
Burial is a thriller, war, horror film directed by Ben Parker.
Set in the last days of World War II, a small band of Russian soldiers led by intelligence officer Brana
Vasilyeva, who is tasked with trafficking the remains of Hitler back to Stalin in Russia.
En route, the unit is attacked by German ‘Werewolf’
partisans and picked off one-by-one.
Brana leads her surviving comrades in a last stand to ensure their ‘cargo’ doesn’t fall into
the hands of those who would see it buried in order to hide the truth forever.
Brana Brodskaya, played by Charlotte Vega.
Mikhail 'Tor' Oleynik, played by Barry Ward.
Cpt. Vadim Ilyasov, played by Dan Renton Skinner.
Iossif Gulyaev, played by Bill Milner.
Dimitry Makar, played by Niall Murphy.
Grigoriy Churakov, played by Kristo Viiding.
The Burial is a 2023 American legal drama film directed by
Maggie Betts and written by Betts and Doug Wright.
It is loosely based on the true story of lawyer Willie E.
Gary and his client Jeremiah Joseph O'Keefe's lawsuit against the Loewen funeral company, as
documented in the 1999 New Yorker article of the same name by Jonathan Harr.
It stars Jamie Foxx as Gary, Tommy Lee Jones as O'Keefe,
Jurnee Smollett, Mamoudou Athie, and Bill Camp.
It premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 11, 2023, and was released by Amazon MGM
Studios in a limited release on October 6, 2023, prior to streaming via Prime Video on October 13, 2023.
The film explores themes of world war ii, joseph stalin,
werewolf, nazi occultism, adolf hitler.
The tone is dark and intense.